via.com.tw 2019-04-13

# Privacy Policy -

This is the privacy notice of VIA Technologies, Inc. In this document, “we”, “our”, or “us” refer to VIA Technologies, Inc.

We are company number 86870786 registered in Taiwan, listed under number 2388 at Taiwan Stock Exchange.

Our headquarters are at 8F, 533 Zhongzheng Rd, Taipei, New Taipei City 231, Taiwan.

* * *

## Introduction

* * *

  1. This is a notice to inform you of our policy about all information that we record about you. It sets out the conditions under which we may process any information that we collect from you, or that you provide to us. It covers information that could identify you (“personal information”) and information that could not. In the context of the law and this notice, “process” means collect, store, transfer, use or otherwise act on information.
  2. We regret that if there are one or more points below with which you are not happy, your only recourse is to leave our website immediately.
  3. We take seriously the protection of your privacy and confidentiality. We understand that all visitors to our website are entitled to know that their personal data will not be used for any purpose unintended by them, and will not accidentally fall into the hands of a third party.
  4. We undertake to preserve the confidentiality of all information you provide to us, and hope that you reciprocate.
  5. Our policy complies with EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
  6. We would like to inform you about your rights and our obligations to you in regards to the processing and control of your personal data.
  7. Except as set out below, we do not share, or sell, or disclose to a third party, any information collected through our website.

* * *

## The bases on which we process information about you

* * *

The law requires us to determine under which of six defined bases we process different categories of your personal information, and to notify you of the basis for each category.

If a basis on which we process your personal information is no longer relevant then we shall immediately stop processing your data.

If the basis changes then if required by law we shall notify you of the change and of any new basis under which we have determined that we can continue to process your information.

### 1\. Information we process because we have a contractual obligation with you

When you create an account on our website, buy a product or service from us, or otherwise agree to our terms and conditions, a contract is formed between you and us.

In order to carry out our obligations under that contract we must process the information you give us. Some of this information may be personal information.

We may use it in order to:

  * Verify your identity for security purposes
  * Sell products to you
  * Provide you with our services
  * Provide you with suggestions and advice on products, services and how to obtain the most from using our website
  * Send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services
  * Follow up with you after correspondence by email or phone call

We process this information on the basis that there is a contract between us, or that you have requested we use the information before we enter into a legal contract.

Additionally, we may aggregate this information in a general way and use it to provide class information, for example to monitor our performance with respect to a particular service we provide. If we use it for this purpose, you as an individual will not be personally identifiable.

We shall continue to process this information until the contract between us ends or is terminated by either party under the terms of the contract.

### 2\. Information we process with your consent

Through certain actions when otherwise there is no contractual relationship between us, such as when you browse our website or ask us to provide you more information about our business, including our products and services, you provide your consent to us to process information that may be personal information.

Wherever possible, we aim to obtain your explicit consent to process this information, for example, by asking you to agree to our use of cookies.

Sometimes you might give your consent implicitly, such as when you send us a message by e-mail to which you would reasonably expect us to reply.

Except where you have consented to our use of your information for a specific purpose, we do not use your information in any way that would identify you personally. We may aggregate it in a general way and use it to provide class information, for example to monitor the performance of a particular page on our website.

If you have given us explicit permission to do so, we may from time to time pass your name and contact information to selected associates whom we consider may provide services or products you would find useful.

We continue to process your information on this basis until you withdraw your consent or it can be reasonably assumed that your consent no longer exists.

You may withdraw your consent at any time by instructing us at [embedded@via.com.tw](mailto:embedded@via.com.tw).

### 3\. Information we process for the purposes of legitimate interests

We may process information on the basis there is a legitimate interest, either to you or to us, of doing so.

Where we process your information on this basis, we do after having given careful consideration to:

  * Whether the same objective could be achieved through other means
  * Whether processing (or not processing) might cause you harm
  * Whether you would expect us to process your data, and whether you would, in the round, consider it reasonable to do so

For example, we may process your data on this basis for the purposes of:

  * Record-keeping for the proper and necessary administration of our online store <http://www.viaembeddedstore.com/>
  * Responding to unsolicited communication from you to which we believe you would expect a response
  * Protecting your interests where we believe we have a duty to do so

### 4.Information we process because we have a legal obligation

We are subject to the law like everyone else. Sometimes, we must process your information in order to comply with a statutory obligation.

For example, we may be required to give information to legal authorities if they so request or if they have the proper authorisation such as a search warrant or court order.

This may include your personal information.

* * *

## Specific uses of information you provide to us

* * *

### 5\. Information relating to your method of payment

Payment information is never taken by us or transferred to us either through our website or otherwise. Our employees and contractors never have access to it.

At the point of payment, you are transferred to a secure page on the website of PayPal. That page may be branded to look like a page on our website, but it is not controlled by us.

### 6\. Sending a message to our support team

When you contact us, whether by telephone, through our website or by e-mail, we collect the data you have given to us in order to reply with the information you need.

We keep personally identifiable information associated with your message, such as your name and email address so as to be able to track our communications with you to provide a high quality service.

* * *

## Use of information we collect through automated systems when you visit our website

* * *

### 7\. Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser when you visit any website. They allow information gathered on one web page to be stored until it is needed for use on another, allowing a website to provide you with a personalized experience and the website owner with statistics about how you use the website so that it can be improved.

Some cookies may last for a defined period of time, such as one day or until you close your browser. Others last indefinitely.

Your web browser should allow you to delete any you choose. It also should allow you to prevent or limit their use.

Our website uses cookies. They are placed by software that operates on our servers, and by software operated by third parties whose services we use.

_When you first visit our website, we ask you whether you wish us to use cookies. If you choose not to accept them, we shall not use them for your visit except to record that you have not consented to their use for any other purpose._

We use cookies in the following ways:

  * To keep you signed in our site
  * To record your answers to surveys and questionnaires on our site while you complete them
  * To help remember and process the items in the shopping cart
  * To keep track of advertisements
  * To compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

**Third-party links**

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google and Facebook, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies and Facebook Pixel) to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### 8\. Personal identifiers from your browsing activity

Requests by your web browser to our servers for web pages and other content on our website are recorded.

We record information such as your geographical location, your Internet service provider and your IP address. We also record information about the software you are using to browse our website, such as the type of computer or device and the screen resolution.

We use this information in aggregate to assess the popularity of the webpages on our website and how we perform in providing content to you.

If combined with other information we know about you from previous visits, the data possibly could be used to identify you personally, even if you are not signed in to our website.

### 9\. Our use of re-marketing

Re-marketing involves placing a cookie on your computer when you browse our website in order to be able to serve to you an advert for our products or services when you visit some other website.

We may use a third party to provide us with re-marketing services from time to time. If so, then if you have consented to our use of cookies, you may see advertisements for our products and services on other websites.

* * *

## Disclosure and sharing of your information

* * *

### 10\. Information we obtain from third parties

Although we do not disclose your personal information to any third party, we sometimes receive data that is indirectly made up from your personal information from third parties whose services we use.

No such information is personally identifiable to you.

### 11\. Data may be processed outside the European Union

Our websites are hosted in the US, Europe, and Taiwan.

We may also use outsourced services in countries outside the European Union from time to time in other aspects of our business.

Accordingly data obtained within the EU or any other country could be processed outside the European Union.

For example, some of the software our website uses may have been developed in the United States of America or in Taiwan.

* * *

## Access to your own information

* * *

### 12\. Access to your personal information

  * At any time you may review or update personally identifiable information that we hold about you.
  * To obtain a copy of any information you may send us a request at [embedded@via.com.tw](mailto:embedded@via.com.tw)
  * After receiving the request, we will tell you when we expect to provide you with the information.

### 13\. Removal of your information

If you wish us to remove personally identifiable information from our website, you may contact us at [embedded@via.com.tw](mailto:embedded@via.com.tw) or follow the instructions at the bottom of each marketing email.

This may limit the service we can provide to you.

### 14\. Verification of your information

When we receive any request to access, edit or delete personal identifiable information we shall first take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or otherwise taking any action. This is important to safeguard your information.

* * *

## Other matters

* * *

### 15\. Use of site by children

  * We do not sell products or provide services for purchase by children, nor do we market to children.
  * We collect data about all users of and visitors to these areas regardless of age, and we anticipate that some of those users and visitors will be children.
  * Such child users and visitors will inevitably visit other parts of the site and will be subject to whatever on-site marketing they find, wherever they visit.

### 16\. Encryption of data sent between us

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) certificates to verify our identity to your browser and to encrypt any data you give us.

Whenever information is transferred between us, you can check that it is done so using SSL by looking for a closed padlock symbol or other trust mark in your browser’s URL bar or toolbar.

### 17\. How you can complain

  * If you are not happy with our privacy policy or have any complaints, please notify us by email at [embedded@via.com.tw](mailto:embedded@via.com.tw).
  * If a dispute is not settled then we hope you will agree to attempt to resolve it by engaging in good faith with us in a process of mediation or arbitration.
  * If you are in any way dissatisfied about how we process your personal information, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the EU Information Commissioner’s Office.

### 18\. Retention period for personal data

Except as otherwise mentioned in this privacy notice, we keep your personal information only for as long as required by us:

  * To provide you with the services you have requested;
  * To comply with other law, including for the period demanded by our tax authorities;
  * To support a claim or defence in court.

### 19\. Compliance with the law

Our privacy policy has been compiled so as to comply with the law of every country or legal jurisdiction in which we aim to do business. If you think it fails to satisfy the law of your jurisdiction, we should like to hear from you.

However, ultimately it is your choice as to whether you wish to use our website.

### 20\. Review of this privacy policy

We may update this privacy notice from time to time as necessary. The terms that apply to you are those posted here on our website on the day you use our website. We advise you to save a copy for your records.

If you have any question regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](mailto:embedded@via.com.tw).

* * *

## **Contacting Us**

* * *

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

8F, 533 Zhongzheng Rd., New Taipei City 231, Taiwan

* * *

###### _Last Edited on 2018-05-24_
